Guide to the Geraldine Page Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Geraldine Page papers
1865-1999
YCAL MSS 774
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
77.84
(88 boxes) + 1 cold storage, 1 record album storage, 1 broadside folder
The papers include personal and professional correspondence, writings, scripts, photographs, legal and financial documents, production programs, personal memorabilia, artwork, audiovisual material, press clippings and other printed material documenting Page's personal life and career as a stage, film, and television actress. Correspondence with family members (including her parents and her husband, the actor Rip Torn), friends, and professional colleagues (including Cheryl Crawford, Elia Kazan, Sissy Spacek, and others), as well as fan mail dates from the 1920s through 1987. Scripts for stage, film, and television include annotated scripts for productions in which she performed as well as scripts sent to her and her husband for review, some accompanied by cover letters. Photographic material includes family portraits and candid photographs, head shots, and production photographs from Page's stage and film productions. Her work is further documented by press clippings and other printed material. Records relating to the production of the films Sweet Bird of Youth and Nasty Habits include contracts, casting call sheets, script pages, and photographs. Also included in the papers are records regarding her work with the Actors Studio and other organizations. The papers also include artwork by Page and others, and personal items including address books, date books, stationery, and articles of clothing.
Page, Geraldine
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Angelica Page Torn on the Eugene G. O'Neill Memorial Fund, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 78, 87-90 (Audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Biographical/Historical note
Geraldine Page was born in Kirksville, Missouri in 1924, and grew up in Chicago where she acted in plays with a church youth group. Following high school she studied at the Goodman Theater School for three years, and with other students from the Goodman formed a stock theater company in which she was active for four seasons. After moving to New York in the late 1940s and working at various odd jobs, she was cast in the 1952 off-Broadway production of Tennessee Williams's Summer and Smoke directed by Jose Quintero. She drew wide praise for her performance, and the following year she made her Broadway debut in Mid-Summer by Vina Delmar. She went on to star in productions on and off-Broadway including The Immoralist (1954), The Rainmaker (1954), Sweet Bird of Youth (1959), Absurd Person Singular (1974), Clothes for a Summer Hotel (1980), Agnes of God (1982), Vivat! Vivat! Regina! (1985), A Lie of the Mind (1985,) and Blithe Spirit (1987). A student of Method acting, she studied at the Actor's Studio, and worked with the Mirror Repertory Company and the Sanctuary Theatre Workshop, Inc.
Page's film work included Hondo (1954), film versions of Summer and Smoke and Sweet Bird of Youth (1962), The Day of the Locust (1975), The Pope of Greenwich Village (1984) and The Trip to Bountiful (1985), for which she won the Academy Award for best actress. On television she appeared in numerous series and television movies, and won Emmy awards for A Christmas Memory (1966) and The Thanksgiving Visitor (1967), both based on stories by Truman Capote.
In addition to the awards mentioned above, Page received numerous nominations for her film and stage work and was the recipient of the Sarah Siddons Award, the British Academy Film Award, and the National Board of Review Award for Best Actress.
Page was married to the violinist Alexander Schneider from 1954 to 1957. She married the actor Rip Torn in 1963, and they had three children, Angelica, Jon and Tony. She died in New York City in 1987.
Scope and Contents
The papers include personal and professional correspondence, writings, scripts, photographs, legal and financial documents, production programs, personal memorabilia, artwork, audiovisual material, press clippings and other printed material documenting Page's personal life and career as a stage, film, and television actress.
Correspondence with family members (including her parents and her husband, the actor Rip Torn), friends, and professional colleagues (including Cheryl Crawford, Elia Kazan, Sissy Spacek, and others), as well as fan mail dates from the 1920s through 1987. Scripts for stage, film, and television include annotated scripts for productions in which she performed as well as scripts sent to her and her husband for review, some accompanied by cover letters. Photographic material includes family portraits and candid photographs, head shots, and production photographs from stage and film productions including Summer and Smoke, Sweet Bird of Youth, Agnes of God, The Trip to Bountiful and others. Her work is further documented by press clippings and other printed material.
Records relating to the production of the films Sweet Bird of Youth and Nasty Habits include contracts, casting call sheets, script pages, and photographs. Also included in the papers are records regarding her work with the Actors Studio, the Poetry Center of the 92nd Street Y, The Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, The New Dramatists Committee and other organizations.
The papers also include artwork by Page and others, and personal items including address books, date books, stationery, and articles of clothing.
Arrangement
Arranged by type of material.
Actors -- United States; Actresses -- United States; Motion picture actors and actresses -- United States; Motion pictures -- Production and direction -- United States; Television -- Production and direction -- United States; Television actors and actresses -- United States; Theater -- United States; Audiovisual materials -- United States -- 20th Century; Photographs -- United States -- 20th Century; Scripts (documents) -- United States -- 20th Century; Actresses -- United States -- 20th Century; Crawford, Cheryl, 1902-1986; Kazan, Elia, 1909-2003; Page, Geraldine; Spacek, Sissy, 1949-; Torn, Rip, 1931-; Actors Studio (New York, N.Y.)
- November 2005 Acquisition, 1865-1999
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 78 (Audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Correspondence, 1933-1987
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1987; 15 (Box 1)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1975; 14 (Box 2)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1963; 15 (Box 3)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1975; 15 (Box 4)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1953-1984; 15 (Box 5)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1953-1984; 15 (Box 6)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1966; 15 (Box 7)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1954-1966; 14 (Box 8)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1953-1970; 12 (Box 9)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1954-1976; 14 (Box 10)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1941-1992; 13 (Box 11)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1954-1992; 12 (Box 12)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1980; 13 (Box 13)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1970; 13 (Box 14)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1933-1986; 10 (Box 15)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1954-1986; 13 (Box 16)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1952-1976; 15 (Box 17)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1950-1968; 13 (Box 18)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1950-1963; 6 (Box 19)
    - Personal correspondence and fan mail, 1963-1967; 6 (Box 20)
    - Telegrams, 1947-1974; 16 (Box 21)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes telegrams from Teresa Wright, Burl Ives, Franchet Tone, Deborah Kerr, Clifford Odets, John Houseman, John Frankenheimer, Billy Rose, Lee Strasberg, Jessica Tandy and Hume Cronyn, Helen Hayes, Pat Boone, Joanne Woodward and Paul Newman, Sammy Davis Jr., Vincent Sardi Jr., Jose Quintero, Ira Levin, James Earl Jones, Molly Kazan, Francis and Miles Davis, Kate Ballard, Joan Blondell and others. Many of the telegrams contain congratulatory messages regarding Page's stage performances.
  - Audience Review cards of Toys in the Attic, undated (Box 22)
  - HB Studio correspondence and printed material, 1965-1973 (Box 22)
  - Printed Material, 1956-1973; 3 (Box 22)
    Includes catalogs, magazines, and booklets.
  - Actors Studio, 1962-1967; 11 (Box 22)
  - Scripts
    Includes play, television, and film scripts, and film treatments, scenarios, etc., predominantly typescript photocopies and mimeograph copies, with related correspondence. Some scripts contain annotations.
    - "Acorns in Moondust," playscript, by Louis La Russo II, undated (Box 23)
    - "Adam," playscript, in three scenes by Marcia Haufrecht, 1974 (Box 23)
    - "Advance Against Royalties," playscript, by Edward Belling (Box 23)
    - "Against Thy Neighbor," playscript, by Roger Smith, 1985 February 5 (Box 23)
    - "All Women Are One," playscript, by Ben Kerner (Box 23)
    - "The American Experience: Program 3, The Emotional Force," television script, by Frank O'Donnell and Jack Lindhorst, 1971 November (Box 23)
    - "...And Other Fragile Things," playscript, by Geraldine Court, 1982 (Box 23)
    - "And Why the Sea is Boiling Hot," playscript, by Arnold Meyer, 1973 (Box 23)
    - "The Arbor (Three Portraits), playscript, by Jonathon Ringkamp, undated (Box 23)
    - "Art Voices in Your Alley," playscript, by "Ronald", undated (Box 23)
    - "Autumn's Family," playscript, by Martin Dulman, 1977 (Box 23)
    - "Bitter Winter (The Last Three Hours)," film script, by Dino Valenti and Warren Paul Langton, 1963 (Box 23)
    - "Booth is Back in Town," playscript, by Austin Pendleton, undated (Box 23)
    - "Brass Birds Don't Sing," playscript, by Samm-Art Williams, 1977 (Box 23)
    - "Brats!," film script, by Kenneth L. Hauser and Ernest Harvey, 1979 January (Box 23)
    - "The Bright and Golden Land," playscript, by Harry Granick, undated (Box 23)
    - "Caina," playscript, by Elinor Cato, 1973 September (Box 23)
    - "Canary in a Chinaberry Tree," playscript, by Jere Admire (Box 23)
    - "Caraway," film script, by Kenneth H. Brown (Box 23)
    - "Candaules, Commissioner," playscript, by Daniel C. Gerould, undated (Box 23)
    - "A Case of Lone Star," film script, by Kinky Friedman and Karen Hicks, 1992 (Box 24)
    - "The Cash Register," playscript, by Lawrence Roman, undated (Box 24)
    - "The Caucasion Chalk Circle," "Mother Courage and Her Children: a Chronicle of the Thirty Years' War," "Galileo," playscript, by Bertold Brecht, 1955 (Box 24)
    - "Chago," film script, by Piri Thomas, 1972 (Box 24)
    - "The Chieftain," film script, by R. Bruce Moody, 1974 (Box 24)
    - "The Chinese and Doctor Fish," playscript, by Murray Schisgal, 1969 (Box 24)
    - "The Chronicles of Bohikee Creek," playscript, by Robert Unger, undated (Box 24)
    - "Clash at Dawn," playscript, by Jack G. Platt, undated (Box 24)
    - "Close Quarters," playscript, adapted by Gilbert Lennox from the play Attentat by W. O. Somin, undated (Box 24)
    - "Come Dressed in Red," playscript, by Melba Thomas, undated; 2 (Box 24)
    - "Come to Glory," Act II, playscript by undidentified author, undated (Box 24)
    - "Corinne," playscript, by Valgene Massey, undated (Box 24)
    - "Crabdance," playscript, by Beverley Simons, undated (Box 24)
    - "Crazy Horse Have Jennie Now," playscript, by Louis Peterson, 1972 (Box 24)
    - "Dance with a Dolly," playscript, by Jack Pulman, undated (Box 24)
    - "Dark Glasses," television script, by John A. Neufeld, undated (Box 24)
    - "Day of Atonement," playscript, by Drew Kalter, undated (Box 24)
    - "The Death and Life of Jesse James," playscript, by Len Jenkin, undated (Box 25)
    - "The Diamond Orchid," playscript, by Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee, 1962 March 10; 3 (Box 25)
    - "The Dinner Party," playscript, by Robert Anglund, 1983 (Box 25)
    - "The Dodo Bird," and "The Peddler," playscript, by Emanuel Fried, undated (Box 25)
    - "The Dream," playscript, by Leonard Speigelglass and Richard Lortz, undated; 2 (Box 25)
    - "Dressed in Clean Clothes," playscript, by Louis C. Adelman, undated (Box 25)
    - "Duet," playscript ,by Robert Sugarman, undated (Box 25)
    - "Dust Whirling with Dust," playscript, by Gus Weill, 1976 (Box 25)
    - "Each Meal, the Last Meal," playscript, by Said Syrafiezadeh, undated (Box 25)
    - "Eat Shit," playscript, by Jack Gelber, 1973 (Box 25)
    - "The Enormous Lie," playscript, by Alvin Aronson, 1958, 1963; 2 (Box 25)
    - "The Eve of the Green Grass," playscript, by Coleman Dowell, undated (Box 25)
    - "The Farewell Party," playscript, by Drew Kalter, 1972 (Box 25)
    - "Fathers and Sons," playscript, by Thomas Babe, 1975 (Box 25)
    - "Fearless Frank," playscript, by Andrew Davies, undated (Box 26)
    - "Film of Memory," playscript, by Paul Osborn, from the novel by Marice Druon, 1963 (Box 26)
    - "Heritage: an American Folk Tale in Two Parts," playscript, by P.J. Barry, 1967 (Box 26)
    - "Forests of the Night," playscript, by Arnold Sundgaard, undated (Box 26)
    - "Four of Them, an Evening of One Act Plays," playscript, by Michael Shurtleff, undated (Box 26)
    - "Friends," playscript, by Eugene Yanni, 1971 (Box 26)
    - "Gales in the Republic," film treatment from the original stories of B. Traven, by Elmore B. Torn and Nancy Audley, 1989; 2 (Box 26)
    - "Gentle Torture Variations," playscript, by Susan Epstein, undated (Box 26)
    - "Good-by and Keep Cold," playscript, by John Ford Noonan, undated (Box 26)
    - "The Gingerbread Boys," film script, by Rudolph Caringi, 1976 (Box 26)
    - "The Happy Bar," playscript, by Kenneth H. Brown, undated (Box 26)
    - "Hedda," playscript, by Edwin Corley, undated (Box 26)
    - "Henhouse," playscript, by Bo Brinkman, 1985 (Box 26)
    - "Herbert's Jumping Off Place," playscript, undated (Box 26)
    - "High Flying Bird," film script, by Milton Moses Ginsberg, 1974 (Box 26)
    - "Homage to Franz Liszt," film script by T. Louis Hammann, undated (Box 26)
    - "The Hunting Party," playscript, by Thomas Bernhard, 1979 (Box 26)
    - "The Hill Wife," television script, by Alfred Brenner, 1957 April 2 (Box 26)
    - "A Husband, a Wife, and a Friend," playscript, by George Furth, undated (Box 26)
    - "If You Love Me," television script, by Fitzroy Davis, undated (Box 26)
    - "I'm Waiting," film script, by Sam Reese, 1976; 2 (Box 27)
    - "Incommunicado," playscript, by Tom Dulack, undated (Box 27)
    - "The Indian Fighters," playscript, by Horton Foote, undated (Box 27)
    - "The Inseparables," playscript, by Harry Granick, undated (Box 27)
    - "Joe Figaro's Wedding," playscript, by Michael Zwerin, undated (Box 27)
    - "The Joy Addict," playscript, by Jay Zimmet, undated (Box 27)
    - "Karl and Arthur," playscript, by Michael Blankfort and Bernard Wolfe, 1975 (Box 27)
    - "The Kids," playscript, by Charles Best, undated (Box 27)
    - "King Saul," playscript, by David R. Slavitt, undated (Box 27)
    - "L. A. Under Siege, playscript, by Mayo Simon, undated (Box 27)
    - "La Loca," playscript, by Ernesto Fuentes, 1959; 2 (Box 27)
    - "The Last Choctaw," film script, by H. H. Madsen, undated (Box 27)
    - "The Light of Life," playscript, by William Packard, 1981 (Box 27)
    - "Like a Garden of Flowers," playscript, by B. J. Roseman, 1963 June 3 (Box 27)
    - "Living," playscript, by Kate Archer, 1976 (Box 27)
    - "The Livingroom," playscript, by Pedro Juan Pietri (Box 27)
    - "The Lonely Passion of Judith Hearne," playscript, by Brian Moore, 1957-1959; 3 (Box 27)
    - "Love Gotta' Come By Saturday Night," playscript, by Ronnie Paris, 1969 September (Box 28)
    - "Madam and the Clown," typescript by Alan Yermanov, undated (Box 28)
    - "Mae West 101, or The Honor of Love," playscript, by Eva Coss, undated (Box 28)
    - "Mary Todd Lincoln," playscript, by M. David Samples, undated (Box 28)
    - "Medea," film script by Paul Mason, adapted from the play by Robinson Jeffers, undated (Box 28)
    - "The Meeting," and "Cruising Speed 600 Miles an Hour," playscripts, by Anna Marie Barlow, undated (Box 28)
    - "The Melancholy Momzer," playscript, by Louis C. Adelman, undated (Box 28)
    - "Mercy Me," playscript, by Jean Reavey, 1967 (Box 28)
    - "Minetti, a Portrait of the Artist as an Old Man," playscript, by Thomas Bernhard, undated (Box 28)
    - "Mr. and Mrs. Television," playscript, by Alfred L. Howard, 1955 June 8 (Box 28)
    - "The Moments of the Wandering Jew," playscript, by David Cole, undated (Box 28)
    - "A Month in the Country," playscript, undated (Box 28)
    - "A Mountain Sleep," playscript, by Edwin Corley, undated (Box 28)
    - "A Mountain of Sundays," playscript, by George and Mary Uhrig, undated (Box 28)
    - "The Mute Who Sang," playscript, undated (Box 28)
    - "Murphy," film script, by William Maidment, adapted from the novel The Last Free Man, 1976 (Box 28)
    - "The Name of the Game, a Sister from Napoli," film script by Peter Allan Fields and Stanley Adams and George F. Slavin, 1970 (Box 28)
    - "The Natural Look," playscript, by Lee Thune, undated (Box 28)
    - "The New Montana," playscript, by Lucille Hauser, 1981, 1983 (Box 28)
    - "Nightwind," playscript, by Ugo Betti, translated from the Italian by A. William Packer, 1945, undated (Box 28)
    - "The Ninth Configuration," film script, by William Peter Blatty, 1975, May (Box 28)
    - "The Nixon Quartet," playscript, by Eric Bentley, 1974 (Box 28)
    - "Notebook of Trigorin", playscript, by Tennesee Williams, a free adaptation of "The Seagull", by Anton Chekov, photocopy, 1981 (Box 29)
    - "Nobody Hears a Broken Drum," playscript, by Jason Miller, undated (Box 29)
    - "Nuts," playscript, by Tom Popor, undated (Box 29)
    - "On the Edge," film script, by Victor B. Miller, adapted from The Desert, by Allen Wheelis, undated (Box 29)
    - "Once Upon Some Trifling Trystings," typescript, by Lynn Applegate, undated (Box 29)
    - "One Eyed King," playscript, by Carlos Fuentes, photocopy, undated (Box 29)
    - "The Operators," television script, by Leonard Abrams, Tim Burns and Lindzee Smith, undated (Box 29)
    - "Other Voyages On a City Street," playscript, by Mary Gannon, undated (Box 29)
    - "Outside Children," film script, by Ben Kerner, 1969 (Box 29)
    - "Overnight," playscript, by William Inge, photocopy, undated (Box 29)
    - "The Passionate Guests," playscript, by John Aristos, undated (Box 29)
    - "People Kill People, Sometimes," television script, by S. Lee Pogostin, 1959 August 19 (Box 29)
    - "The People vs. Inez Garcia," playscript, by Rena Down, 1975 (Box 29)
    - "Philoctetes 11," playscript, by Robert Lesser, undated (Box 29)
    - "The Philosophy of Socrates Smith," typescript, edited by L. Elwin Page, undated (Box 29)
    - "The Place Where We Were Born," playscript, by Ettore Rella, undated (Box 29)
    - "Playback," film script, by Fred Barron, 1976 (Box 29)
    - "A Present From Your Old Man," playscript, by Walter Crittenden, undated (Box 29)
    - "Primal Urge," film script, by Peter A. Beltz and John Clayton, 1990 August (Box 30)
    - "Princess Grace and the Fazzaris," playscript, by Marc Alan Zagoren, 1978 (Box 30)
    - "The Pocket Watch," playscript, by Alvin Aronson, 1956 (Box 30)
    - "Quantum Dog in a Deep Blue Jaguar," playscript, by Stephen J. Goldberg, 1994 (Box 30)
    - "Quote, Unquote," playscript, by Ben Starr, undated (Box 30)
    - "A Rain of Ashes," film script, by John Peacock and John Veltri, 1965 (Box 30)
    - "A Recent Killing," playscript, by Leroy Jones, undated (Box 30)
    - "Red River, Red Rover," playscript, by Ken McGuire, undated (Box 30)
    - "Reunion," film script, by Sharon Spitz and Joe Giannone, 1985 (Box 30)
    - "Ricky Lee," playscript, by Roger Smith, undated (Box 30)
    - "Risking," film script, by Dorothy Ames, 1982 (Box 30)
    - "Robocop 3," film script, by Frank Miller and Fred Dekker, 1991 January 28 (Box 30)
    - "Rocky Mountain Fever," film script, by W. W. Red Lewis, undated (Box 30)
    - "September Equinox," playscript, by Roger-Marius Carre, undated (Box 30)
    - "The Shanglers," playscript, by Betsy Julia Robinson, 1976 August (Box 30)
    - "This Side of the Door," playscript, a "Stanley Award Play,", 1913 July 13 (Box 30)
    - "The Silent Partner," playscript, by Clifford Odets, undated (Box 30)
    - "Sister," playscript, by Glenn Allen Smith, undated (Box 31)
    - "The Skinwearers," playscript, by Joel Friedman, undated (Box 31)
    - "Song for October," playscript, by Robert Hill, undated (Box 31)
    - "Sorrel's Own," film script, by Douglas Camfield, undated (Box 31)
    - "Splendid Rebel," film script, by Ernest A. Joselovitz, 1974, 1976 (Box 31)
    - A Streetcar named Desire by Tennesee Williams, photocopy of published script (2 copies), undated; 2 (Box 31)
    - "The Saddest Summer of Samuel's," playscript, by J. P. Donleavy, undated (Box 31)
    - "Switzerland," film script, by T. H. Elmore (Box 31)
    - "The Tall Green Grass," playscript, by Louis C. Adelman, undated (Box 31)
    - "Tatiana Golikova is Real," playscript, by Kaye Kynion, undated (Box 31)
    - "The Thousand Guns of Justin Malloy," film script, by Elliot Monet, undated (Box 31)
    - "This is My Story/This is Mine," playscript, by Shirley Lauro, 1978 (Box 31)
    - "Three Houses on Craven Run," film script, by Ben Canfield, undated (Box 31)
    - "The Three Sisters," playscript, by Anton Chekhov, undated (Box 31)
    - "Three Sisters," playscript, photocopy, undated (Box 31)
    - "Three to Tango," playscript, by L. Hauser, undated (Box 31)
    - "The Tree," film script, by Robert Guenete, undated (Box 32)
    - "The Tumbleweed Wagon," film script, by Russ Marker, 1989 March 29 (Box 32)
    - "The Uninvited," motion picture treatment by Charles Trischmann, 1976 (Box 32)
    - "Up and Down," "In and out," playscripts, by James Luczak, 1981 August (Box 32)
    - "War in Heaven," playscript, by Philip Barry, undated (Box 32)
    - "Wasn't it a Lovely Funeral," motion picture treatment, by Richard Sanders Rosenthal, undated (Box 32)
    - "Waiting for Henry Plummer," playscript, by E. P. Conkle, undated (Box 32)
    - Walter's Waste," playscript, by Will Allen, 1972 (Box 32)
    - "Where the Green Banans Grow," playscript, undated (Box 32)
    - "Where's Annie?," typescript, undated; 2 (Box 32)
    - "Within Dark Rooms," playscript, by Sal Messina, undated (Box 32)
    - "Wooing Miss Swarz," playscript, by Jay Zimmet, undated (Box 32)
    - "Works and Days," film script, by Rudy Caringi, 1974; 2 (Box 32)
    - "A World Where Boredom Reigns," playscript, by Edouard Pailleron, 1985 (Box 32)
    - "The Yellow Dog Contract," film script, by Edward Setrakian, 1979 (Box 32)
    - Untitled scripts, undated; 5 (Box 32)
    - Untitled scripts, undated; 7 (Box 33)
    - Untitled writings, undated; 3 (Box 33)
  - Production photographs of Geraldine Page from the stage production Clothes for a Summer Hotel, 1983; 7 (Box 33)
  - Production photographs of Geraldine Page from plays and films, also includes publicity photographs., undated; 11 (Box 34)
  - Personal correspondence with Robert Casper, 1953-1964; 10 (Box 35)
  - Personal correspondence with family, friends and associates, 1952-1986; 9 (Box 35)
    Includes clippings, photographs and ephemera
  - Personal correspondence with family and associates, 1912-1964; 8 (Box 36)
  - Personal papers, family history and photographs, 1917-1958; 7 (Box 36)
  - Velvet box, undated (Box 36)